You're kidding me.
（木渡(きわたり)）バカな！
ブタに2500万も
賭けたっていうのか？
She bet 25 million yen on a pig?
（芽亜里(めあり)）ウフッ まあね
That's right.
３ターン目の夢子(ゆめこ)の勝ちは
露骨だったから 気付くと思ったよ
Yumeko's win in turn three was so obvious
I figured you'd catch on.
私にとっても 苦しいところだった
It was painful for me too.
チェッ
なに 調子に乗ってやがる！
What makes you think you've won?
You've only beat me for one round.
まだ１回勝っただけだろうが！
As long as I've got something to bet,
I'll never lose to a moron like you.
いいんだよ これで
賭ける弾さえあれば
お前みたいなクソバカに
負けるわけない
What did you say?
（木渡）んだと！
（清華(さやか)）言うまでもないことですが
I shouldn't need to say this,
but violence is strictly forbidden.
暴力行為は禁止ですので
（木渡）でっ…
（清華）早乙女(さおとめ)様も
- Saotome, please don't provoke him.
- Right.
挑発するような発言は
慎まれますよう…
はいはい
では５ターン目 参ります
On to turn five, then.
（木渡）
家畜の分際(ぶんざい)で…
Stupid house pet.
I'll take everything you've got.
丸裸にしてやる
I'm betting one Kiwatari chip.
ベット 木渡１枚！
Call...
（奈々美(ななみ)）
コー… あっ フ… フォールド
I mean, fold.
（夢子）レイズ 木渡４枚
Raise. Four Kiwatari chips.
（木渡）
うっ いや待て これはブラフだ
No, wait. This is a bluff.
コール 木渡１枚 蕾(つぼみ)２枚
Call. One Kiwatari chip,
two Tsubomi chips.
（芽亜里）ウフフ…
Reveal your hands, then.
（清華）
では 手札を開示してください
７ ９のブタ！
Pig. Seven and nine.
（木渡）
ブラフだったら まず勝てる
ヤツは…
If she was bluffing, I should win.
- She's...
- A suit with two and five.
ウフフ… ２ ５のマークです
ぐっ
ふ〜ん
ベット 木渡３枚
Bet. Three Kiwatari chips.
（木渡）
ぐっ… また高額ベットだと？
Another high-stakes bet?
I've got a pig.
俺の手はブタ
勝負にいける手じゃない
I can't risk it.
フォールドだ
Fold.
- Lucky me! I had a pig and still won!
- What?
ラッキー
ブタなのに
勝っちゃった！
（木渡）
なに！ ふ… ふざけてやがる
You're kidding me.
読みが鋭いとか
ブラフがうまいとか
This goes way beyond being good
at reading expressions or bluffing.
そういう問題を超えてる！
あっ まさか！
Don't tell me...
You finally noticed?
You know, you really are dumb.
（芽亜里）
やっと気付いたか
お前さ ホント バカだね
Tsubomi,
（夢子）
蕾さん 木渡さんに命令されて
やっているのでしょうが
I imagine Kiwatari is telling you
to do this, but you should stop.
やめたほうがいいですよ
“伏せたカードの置き方で
マークを伝える”なんて
Changing the position of your card
to tell him he has a suit is too obvious.
あまりにも分かりやすいですから
From what you've done so far,
straight means spade.
今までの手を考えると
垂直でスペード
Slight right means club.
右に僅かに傾けるとクラブ
Left means diamond.
左でダイヤ
そして 一旦置いた物を
前に滑らせると ハートですね
And if you put it down and slide it,
it's a heart.
What was this about
how house pets can't fool humans?
何が“家畜のやることなんて
見え透いてる”だよ
お前のやってることなんて
もっとあからさまじゃん
What you're doing is even more obvious.
I know for a fact
that in Year Two, Camellia Class,
知ってるぞ
２年椿(つばき)組じゃ 家畜の蕾奈々美が
お前のグループに小間使いにされて
Nanami Tsubomi
is your group's personal plaything.
見せ物のように扱われてるってな
組分けが発表されたときは
さすがに焦ったよ
When the teams were announced,
I got a little worried.
I knew you two would be working together.
木渡と蕾… 確実にグルだ
So...
だから…
夢子に協力してもらったってわけ
I decided to have Yumeko help me.
〜
ウフフ
油断していたのでしょうが
I think you let your guard down.
When you checked the card,
you let your emotions show.
カードを確認する一瞬
感情が出てましたよ
主人が無能では
Don't you feel bad for Tsubomi,
having such an idiot for a master?
蕾さんが
かわいそうでは ありませんか？
Shut up.
うるせえ！
（夢子）蕾さん
Tsubomi, I'll show you
a better way to do it.
いい方法を教えてあげます
You put your hands under the desk
こうやって机の下で 指で
お互いのカードを教え合うんです
and use your fingers
to tell each other your cards.
That's much safer.
それなら確実でしょう？
（奈々美）はっ くっ…
なに！ ナメやがって！
Why, you little...
It seems that everyone is cheating
in some manner.
どうやら全員が
何らかのイカサマを
行っているようですね
Now, how to deal with this...
さて どう扱ったものか…
（夢子）五十嵐(いがらし)さん
Igarashi,
I'm not saying anything
about Kiwatari and Tsubomi's cheating.
私は 木渡さんと蕾さんの
イカサマを指摘しません
指摘しなければ
止める理由はありませんよね？
If I don't, there's no reason
to stop us, right?
I see.
なるほど
So, you want to enjoy a game
with cheating?
イカサマありの状態で
ゲームを楽しみたい
Is that right?
ということですね
イカサマありのほうが
面白いと思うんです
I think this game is more fun
with cheating.
このゲームは
あっ 木渡さんは
化かし合いは苦手ですか？
Oh, are you not good at games
where you trick each other, Kiwatari?
バカ正直に手札を明かして
くださってましたものね
You were basically telling us
what was in your hand, right?
Fine.
（木渡）上等だよ
さっさと続けるぞ！
Let's keep going.
ウフフ 面白くなってきましたね
This is getting interesting.
全員が自分の手札を
完全に認識している
Everyone knows exactly
what's in their hand.
もはや この勝負
ブラフ合戦と成り果てました！
This game is now
just a big series of bluffs!
いいでしょう
ゲームを再開します
Very well.
I'm resuming the game.
DEBT - 310 MILLION YEN
（清華）
ウフッ この卓は
うそにまみれている
This table is covered with lies.
And the best liar will win the victory.
うそを制した者が
勝利をつかむことでしょう
（奈々美）
あっ マークの７ ８
A seven, eight suit...
Tsubomi, you play.
蕾 お前 勝負しろ！
（奈々美）はっ はい
Okay!
- Call...
- No, you idiot, raise!
（奈々美）コー…
（木渡）バカ野郎！
違うだろ レイズだ！
少しは頭を働かせろ！
Use your head!
You're the idiot.
（芽亜里）バカは あんただろ？
強い手が来たって
私たちに教えてどうすんだよ
Even if you have a good hand,
why are you telling us?
- Fold.
フォールド！
こっ この…
Why...?
Shit. She's slowing me down.
（木渡）
クソが…
足を引っ張りやがって！
現在のトップは夢子だ
Yumeko is in the lead.
I took on debt to be here.
俺は借金をして
ここにいる
１位じゃなきゃ
借金が確定し
If I don't win, the debt will be real
and I'll be a house pet. Me, a house pet?
家畜に落ちる
この俺が家畜だと？
ありえない
Impossible. I'm an owner, not a pet.
I'll make them understand.
俺は飼う側の人間
それを分からせてやる
Call. One Saotome chip.
コール 早乙女１枚
ふ〜ん
ここで勝負ってことは
自信のある手なのかな？
If you're going for it,
you must have confidence in your hand.
な〜んてね
Just kidding!
If you were really confident,
you'd be betting one of Jabami's chips!
本当に自信があったら
蛇喰(じゃばみ)チップを賭けるっつうの！
は〜い 残念
Too bad!
A pair? Now?
（木渡）
ここでペアだと？
何なんだよ〜
What the hell is going on here?
Why is this happening to me?
なんで俺が こんな理不尽な目に…
では９ターン 参ります
Now, moving on to turn nine...
（木渡）ハア ハア ハア ハア
I have two turns left
and I'm in third place.
（木渡）
残り２ターン 現状３位
If this doesn't change,
I'll end up with 50 million in debt!
このまま順位が確定すれば
借金額は５千万
（木渡）蕾！
（奈々美）はい！
- Tsubomi!
- Yes?
Bet a Jabami chip!
蛇喰チップを賭けろ！
えっ でっ でも…
But...
Shut up and do it!
いいから やれ！
お前のチップを俺に移せ！
Give me your chip!
俺の足ばっかり
引っ張りやがって！
You keep screwing things up,
so be useful for once!
少しは役に立て！
（奈々美）はい
Okay.
コール 蛇喰１枚… です
Call. One Jabami Chip.
（夢子）コール 木渡１枚
Call. One Kiwatari chip.
フォールド
Fold.
Yumeko, you must have a good hand.
（木渡）
夢子 いい手が来たか…
しかし ここは 絶対に引けない
But I won't drop out here.
Once I have Tsubomi's chip,
I'm almost certain to get first place.
蕾のチップが手に入れば
１位は ほぼ確定
There's no bluffing here. This is just
a pure bet on the cards themselves!
ここは駆け引きもクソもない
純然たるカードの勝負
では 手札を開示してください
Please reveal your hands.
うっ あ…
７ ５のマークだ
A seven, five suit.
６ ２のマークです
A six, two suit.
（木渡）ぐっ…
What?
クッ
フフッ フハハハ アハハハ…
I won!
勝った 勝ったぞ！
蛇喰チップ５枚 １億5500万！
I have 5 Jabami chips or 155 million yen!
First place is mine! That's what you get.
ぶっちぎりの１位だ
ざま見ろ てめえら
明日から地獄を見せてやる
Starting tomorrow,
I'll make your lives hell.
ウフフ ギャンブルの結果は
最後まで分からないものですよ
You don't know how
the game will end until it's over.
（木渡）はあ？
では10ターン 参ります
Moving on to turn ten.
For better or for worse, this is the end.
泣いても笑っても これが最後
皆様 悔いのなきよう
お賭けください
Everyone, make sure you don't regret this.
It's over already?
もう おしまいですか？
何だか時間が早く
過ぎたような気がします
It feels like time went so fast.
もっと やっていたいくらい
I could keep playing forever.
私はもう ごめんだね
I'm tired of this.
Let's just finish this up.
こんなギャンブル
さっさと終わらそう
What? Why are they so calm?
（木渡）
なに 何なんだ
こいつらの余裕は！
I'm folding this turn,
so first place is mine for sure.
このターンは
降りるから
俺の１位は確定して…
うっ！
No, wait...
いや 待て… あるじゃねえか
There's an easy way for them
to get first place.
ヤツらが簡単に１位になる手が！
例えば 早乙女に
蛇喰チップを全て賭けさせた上で
For instance, Yumeko could make Saotome
bet all her Jabami chips and win,
夢子が勝てばいい
逆もしかりだ
or the other way around.
どうする？
What do I do? How do I do this?
No, there's only one way.
どうすれば…
いや どうもこうもない
俺か蕾が勝つことが
唯一 防ぐ手だ
The only way to stop them is for me
or Tsubomi to win. I can win this.
来い 勝てる手！
わっ
フフッ
Tsubomi has a pair of nines?
This time I win for sure.
（木渡）
蕾に９のゾロ目だと？
今度こそ間違いなく
俺の勝ちだ！
ベット 早乙女１枚
Bet. One Saotome chip.
（夢子）う〜ん
（木渡）
フッ ヘヘッ せいぜい考えて選べ
Think carefully. Whether you bet or not,
you're going to be at least third place!
賭けようが賭けまいが
お前の３位以下は確定だ
コール 蛇喰１枚
Call. One Jabami chip.
（木渡）
あっ 蛇喰１枚… だと？
One Jabami chip?
（芽亜里）はあ 何やってんの!?
What are you doing?
黙ってりゃ勝てるのに！
- All we had to do is keep quiet.
- Isn't it kind of irritating right now?
（夢子）だって このままでは
何だか腹立たしいでは
ありませんか？
私は 蕾さんが勝つほうに賭けます
I'm betting on Tsubomi winning.
Won't you help me?
早乙女さんも
協力していただけませんか？
（芽亜里）はあ？ なんで私が！
- Why would I do that?
- What are they talking about?
（木渡）
何の話をしている？
（夢子）ウフフ ウフフ
（芽亜里）
ああ 分かった
分かったよ もう！
Fine! I'll play along
with this stupid game of yours.
あんたの悪趣味に
つきあってあげる
Raise. Three Jabami chips.
レイズ 蛇喰３枚
（木渡）
蛇喰チップが５枚！
Five Jabami chips.
蕾が勝ったら １億７千万!?
If Tsubomi wins, she gets 170 million?
ひいっ
俺を抜いちまうじゃねえか！
She'll have more than me!
（奈々美）あ…
（木渡）降りろ 蕾！
Fold, Tsubomi!
I'll never let you beat me!
俺に勝つなんて てめえ
ぜってえ許さねえからな！
Fold!
降りろ！
は… はい
Okay.
（夢子）蕾さん
（奈々美）あっ
Tsubomi, is it okay
to let him keep abusing you?
虐げられたままで いいのですか？
Are you just telling yourself
you have to endure it until graduation?
卒業するまで耐えきればいいと
自分を正当化しているのでは
ありませんか？
（奈々美）あ…
That way of thinking is wrong.
その考えは間違っています
理不尽に対して
あらがえない人間の性質は
If a person doesn't fight
against injustice, nothing will change.
一生そのまま
それこそ 一生家畜ですよ
You'll be house pet your whole life.
Will you live your life
with your head down forever?
今後 一生 こうべを垂れて
生きるのですか？
蕾！ さっさと降りろ！
Tsubomi, fold, damn it!
学園のルールだから 普段は
しかたないのかもしれません
Maybe normally you have to obey
the school's rules.
しかし
But you've got a chance to fight back.
If you don't take it...
こうやって あらがうチャンスが
目前に転がっているのに
拾わないのは
おりが開いているのに
そこから出ないブタと同じ
you're like a pig who refuses
to walk through an open cage door.
自らが家畜であると
You're proving to everyone
that you're really a house pet.
証明しているようなものでは
ありませんか？
I...
（奈々美）わ… 私…
ああ それとも…
Or is that how you want to live your life?
それこそが
あなたの生き方なのでしょうか？
理不尽にあらがうのは怖い
You're too scared to fight back.
だったら こびを売って
You'd rather suck up to him,
so he'll be a little nicer to you.
少しでも
優しくしてもらったほうがいい
ウフフ
なるほど それも世渡りのひとつ
なのかもしれませんね
I see. That may be one way to live,
though it's one I can't understand at all.
私には全く理解できませんが
でしたら 木渡さんの機嫌を
損なわないうちに
Then you should get out fast,
before you make Kiwatari madder, right?
早いところ
降りたほうがいいですよ ね？
Right? Tsubomi, the permanent house pet?
一生家畜の蕾さん
Shut up!
（奈々美）うるさい！ うるさい！
うるさい！
You don't know anything!
何も…
何も知らないくせに！
何も！
You don't...
（生徒Ａ）わあ きれい
Wow, it's so pretty!
（生徒Ｂ）すご〜い
It's amazing!
I'm so jealous.
（生徒Ｃ）いいなあ！
（生徒Ａ）ね〜
Right? It's so silky smooth.
（生徒Ｂ）サラサラだよ〜
Like a doll's.
（生徒Ｃ）お人形さんみた〜い
（生徒Ｂ）
ねえ いつから伸ばしてるの？
- How long have you been growing it?
- Since I was in elementary school.
うん 小学生のときからだよ
（生徒Ａ）ホント きれいだよね！
It really is pretty.
（生徒たち）
ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ…
Mittens!
（奈々美）
いや！ やめて… いや やめて！
No! Stop it!
まあ まあ 落ち着けって
Calm down. We're not going to hurt you.
別に乱暴しようってわけじゃねえ
はっ！
We're just gonna give you a little trim.
ちょっと髪を切るだけだ
あっ！
No!
いや〜！
どうして…
Why?
どうして
どう… して
こんな ひどいこと するの？
Why are you doing something so awful?
あ？ 前から長い髪を
切ってみたかったんだよ
I always wanted to cut your long hair.
伸び過ぎた爪を切るときって
何か気持ちいいだろ？
Doesn't it feel good when you cut nails
that have gotten too long?
It's the same thing!
それと同じだ
The threads that held me up snapped.
（奈々美）
私を支える糸が切れた
After that,
それ以降
私は心を安定させるために
to keep myself sane,
自分の気持ちを
心の中で押し潰した
I kept my feelings locked up inside me.
でも 今日 今だけは違う
But... today, right now,
things are different.
私の意思ひとつで
この男に大きな損害を与えられる
With one choice,
I can make him suffer a terrible loss.
押し殺していた感情が よみがえる
The feelings I locked up are returning.
The fear I felt that day, the loss,
the rage, the frustration...
あの日の恐れ 喪失感 怒り
悔しさ 復しゅう心
the desire for... revenge!
私は！
I...
I'm...
私は！
私は家畜じゃない！
I'm not a house pet!
私は 人間だ！
I'm a human!
THE GIRL WHO BECAME HUMAN
コール！
Call!
ハア ハア
（木渡）蕾〜！
Tsubomi!
暴力行為は慎むよう
お願いしたはずですが
I believe I asked you
to refrain from violence.
（木渡）くっ… えい！
You're going to regret this later.
てめえ あとで覚えてろよ ぐっ…
This is certainly a surprise.
（清華）
随分と意外な展開になったもの
やはり会長のおっしゃることは
全部正しい
As usual, everything the student council
president said was correct.
蛇喰夢子は狂っている
Yumeko Jabami is insane.
Sanity will get you nowhere with her.
理屈では計れない
（木渡）
てっ こいつ 頭 おかしいのか？
Is she crazy?
What's the point of making Tsubomi win?
蕾に勝負させることに
何の意味が！
待てよ 意味なんてないのか？
Wait, maybe there is no point.
つまり夢子の手は 必ず勝てる手
Maybe Yumeko's got a hand
that can't lose. A pair of tens.
10のペア まさか…
No way.
（清華）
それでは 手札を開示してください
Please reveal your hands.
ウフッ これで終わりかと思うと
何だか名残惜しいですね
It's kind of a shame to think it's over.
２ 10のブタです
- A two, ten. Pig.
- A pair of nines.
（木渡）ああ？
（奈々美）はあ
９のペアです
まあ！
Oh, my!
What a great hand for the last round.
この土壇場で
すごい手が来ましたね
Congratulations!
おめでとうございます！
She's insane.
How much did she bet on a pig?
（木渡）
いかれてやがる
ブタに いくら賭けたんだ
こいつは！
チッ
２位ってことは
If I'm second place.
I'm out 10 million yen.
結局
マイナス１千万円か！
Well, that doesn't matter.
I can get that amount of money.
まあ いい
この程度 何とでもなる
The bigger problem is the fact
that she disobeyed me.
それよりも この女が
逆らったことのほうが問題だ
二度と反抗する気も起こらないよう
グチャグチャにしてやる！
I'll make sure she never fights back.
皆様 お疲れさまでした
Congratulations, everyone.
全10ターン終了です
All ten turns are complete.
これより 結果発表に参ります
I will now announce the results.
The winner...
栄えある１位は…
早乙女芽亜里様
is Mary Saotome,
獲得額は
１億６６００万円です
with 166 million yen.
２位 蕾奈々美様
Second place is Nanami Tsubomi,
with 92 million yen.
（清華）９２００万円
（木渡）おっ おい
Hey, wait!
（清華）３位 蛇喰夢子様
Third place is Yumeko Jabami...
（清華）７４００万円
（木渡）ちょ… 待て！
- Hey!
- ...with 74 million yen.
（清華）
４位 木渡 潤(じゅん)様 5800万円
- Fourth place is Jun Kiwatari...
- Wait! You're getting this wrong!
（木渡）間違ってるぞ
わ… 訳 分かんねえこと
言ってんじゃねえぞ ボケ！
You're not making a damn bit of sense!
結果に間違いございません
The results are correct.
Like hell they are!
I've got five Jabami chips!
ふざけんな！
俺は蛇喰チップを５枚持ってる！
That's way above 58 million on its own!
これだけでも 5800万なんて
余裕で超えてるんだろうが！
（芽亜里）ププッ クク…
Saotome, it's rude to laugh too much.
早乙女さん あんまり笑っちゃ
かわいそうですよ
うっ あ？
（芽亜里）アッ ハハハハ！
（夢子）ウフフ…
I didn't think it would work so well!
こんなに うまくいくとはね〜
Part of it was luck, but a lot of it
was thanks to your acting!
運も良かったですが
早乙女さんの演技力も見事でしたよ
Yeah? Thanks!
そう？ ありがと！
（木渡）だっ
まだ気付かないわけ？
You still didn't figure it out?
Do the math.
計算してみなよ
額がピッタリ入れ替わってる
チップがあるっしょ？
Two sets of chips
have their values swapped, right?
はあ？ チップ… だと？
The chips?
JABAMI
God, you're slow at math.
計算 おっせ〜
もういい　教えてあげる
All right, I'll tell you.
これ 私と夢子の逆だから
Yumeko's and mine are switched.
夢子のチップが 500万円で
私のチップが 3100万円ってこと
Yumeko's chips are worth 5 million yen,
and mine are worth 310 million.
どう？ そしたら計算合うっしょ？
See? The math works, right?
Don't be stupid. You can't just...
バ… バカ言え！ そんなこと…
ルール説明にあったでしょ？
It was in the rules, right?
You can write your own amount of debt.
借金額は あくまで“自己申告”
つまり 夢子は
３億１千万円の借金のうち
In other words, Yumeko only reported
5 million of her 310 million yen debt.
あえて5000万だけ申告
対して私の借金は５千万だけど
And I have 50 million in debt,
but I reported it as 310 million.
３億１千万と申告した
You said on your application that you took
10 million from a friend, right?
あんたも うその申告で
友達に１千万
受け取らせたんでしょ？
私たちも同じことをやっただけ
We did the same thing.
うそつきは
あんただけじゃなかったんだよ
You weren't the only liar.
An acquaintance of mine
should be getting the money now.
今頃 知り合いが 私の分のお金を
受け取ってるはずだよ
（生徒）鈴井(すずい)さん
Suzui, message from the student council.
生徒会からのお届け物です
（鈴井）げ！ な… 何だ これ！
What the hell is this?
The rest was simple.
（芽亜里）
ここまでやれば あとは簡単な話
私の手元に３億１千万
I received a board
that read "310 million yen,"
夢子に５千万のボードが来る
and Yumeko got one
that said "50 million."
だから それを交換するだけ
So, we just switched.
And then, how strange...
すると あら不思議！
私と夢子のチップの額が
入れ替わるってわけ
The values of our chips were switched.
ウフッ
I can't believe you fell for it so easily!
こんなに見事に
だまされてくれるとはね
This is stupid!
バ… バカな！
おい こんなのルール違反だろ！
Hey, this is against the rules, right?
自分のボードを自分の前に
掲げなければならない—
There's no rule that says you must place
your own board in front of you.
というルールはありません
That's insane! It's 260 million yen!
おかしいだろ！
２億６千万だぞ！
そんな額の虚偽申告を受け入れて
What's in it for the student council,
生徒会に
何のメリットがあるんだよ！
accepting a fake application
with an amount like that?
That's none of your business.
（清華）
あなたの知ったことでは
ありませんね
ぐっ お…
Kiwatari, it's a mistake to judge things
only by your own standards.
木渡さん
自分の枠だけで
物事を判断するのは
いけませんよ
人間は皆
それぞれ違うのですから
Every person is different.
There are some things they can forgive
and some things they can't.
許せることも 許せないことも
100パーセント あなたの意思に
沿う人間なんていない
No one will ever obey you 100 percent.
That's what makes it so great, right?
だから いいのでしょう？
Shut up! I refuse to accept this!
（木渡）ふ… ふざけんな！
こんなもの 認めねえぞ 俺は！
Your permission is unnecessary.
あなたの許可などいりません
We're simply recording the results
as they occurred.
我々は順位に従って
処理するのみです
（芽亜里）
アハハ
だまされたお前がアホなの！
It's your fault for being stupid enough
to get tricked.
You bitch!
（木渡）てめえ〜！
あっ がが…
あが〜
あっ ががが…
暴力行為は禁止
Violence is forbidden.
That's the third time you were told.
３回目です
ががが…
そんなことより
理解しているのですか？
More importantly, do you understand?
You are now 310 million in debt
to the student council.
あなたは我が生徒会に対し
３億１千万の負債を負いました
返せない場合 あなたは…
If you can't pay it off...
you're going to be a house pet!
家畜となります！
（木渡）ぐわ〜！
では これで
手続きは完了となります
That's the last of the paperwork.
Thank you, everyone.
お疲れさまでした
（芽亜里）
あ〜 終わった 終わった！
It's all done.
（夢子）そうそう 蕾さん
（奈々美）あ…
Oh, right.
Tsubomi.
先ほどの心意気を
忘れないでくださいね
Don't forget how you felt back there.
はあ…
（奈々美）
私は 結局２位
I only got second place.
家畜のままだし
借金額は変わらず２千万円
I'm still a house pet,
and I still owe 20 million yen.
ウフフ だまされた…
I was fooled.
But I don't feel any anger.
（奈々美）
でも 怒りなんてない
夢子さんは きっかけをくれたんだ
Yumeko gave me a chance.
（芽亜里）
とまあ そういうわけだからさ
So, that's how it happened.
Can I have that check back?
その小切手 返してくれない？
（芽亜里）
少額ならともかく ２億６千万だ
A small amount is one thing,
but that's 260 million yen.
鈴井が変な気を起こさないとも…
Suzui might start getting ideas.
アハハ そういうことだったんだ
So, that was it.
I thought it was a joke and got scared.
何の冗談かと思って ビビったよ
はい
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
（夢子）ありがとうございます
（鈴井）いや〜
It's amazing that you could win
such a big gamble.
そんな大勝負に勝つなんて
すごいね　おめでとう
- Congratulations, both of you.
- It's almost hilarious how honest he is.
（芽亜里）
バカ正直も
ここまでくると笑えるな
じゃ 私はこれで
Okay, I'll be going.
（夢子）えいっ
えっ な… 何！
What?
Thank you!
ありがとうございました
Thanks to your help,
I was able to enjoy a stimulating game.
あなたの提案のおかげで
刺激的なゲームができました
ん… ま… まあ
それはお互いさま
Well, that goes for both of us.
Now, get off me!
Where are you touching me?
つか 離れろ！
どこ触ってんのよ！
Oh, I'm sorry.
（夢子）あら これは失礼しました
ウフフ 早乙女さん
Saotome, is it all right
if I call you Mary?
よろしければ“芽亜里さん”と
呼ばせていただいても
よろしいですか？
私たち
お友達になりましたでしょう？
We're friends now, right?
えっ べ… 別に
Well, that's...
うわっ あ…
別に… いいけど
That's fine, I guess.
わあ！ ありがとうございます
芽亜里さん！
Thank you, Mary!
うっ ちょっ まあ…
もう引っ付くな！
- Get off me!
- Mary!
（鈴井）
何か すごい仲良くなってる？
They're much friendlier than before.
（夢子）芽亜里さん 芽亜里さん…
（清華）
ゲームの結果は
想定内に収まるものだった
The game ended in the way we expected.
というよりも
It didn't matter to us, either way.
我々としては どちらでもよかった
木渡は県知事の息子で
Kiwatari is the son of a governor.
Yumeko is on our list of people to watch.
蛇喰夢子は要注意人物
どちらかが相手を陥れ
We wanted one to defeat the other.
片方を大敗させるのが狙いだった
So, the result was a success.
だから結果は成功
しかし これでよかったのか？
But was this right?
That last turn, Yumeko Jabami
volunteered to go to third place,
ラストのターン
蛇喰夢子は自ら３位へ下り
taking a 30 million yen loss.
金額にして３千万円の損をのんだ
Money doesn't drive her.
彼女は金を行動原理としない
もっとも簡易に人を操る手段が
通用しないということだ
The simplest way to control people
won't work on her.
President...
会長…
蛇喰夢子の手綱を手放してしまって
本当によかったのでしょうか？
was it right to let go of her reins?
ああ
〜
（豆生田(まにゅうだ)）
蛇喰夢子の人生計画表を
You're refusing to rescind
Yumeko Jabami's life plan?
取り下げない？
Someone you could never understand...
（鈴井）
どちらかが撃たれることは 確実
Don't worry about a thing. Let's just
enjoy ourselves as much as we can!
（妄(みだり)）
お前は 何も心配しなくていい
心行くまで 楽しもうぜ〜！
EPISODE 6: THE INVITING GIRL